♪ ♪
♪ IF THE RAIN COMES THEY
RUN AND HIDE THEIR HEADS ♪
♪ THEY MIGHT AS
WELL BE DEAD ♪
♪ IF THE RAIN COMES,
IF THE RAIN COMES ♪
♪ WHEN THE SUN SHINES
THEY SLIP INTO THE SHADE ♪
♪ (WHEN THE SUN
SHINES DOWN) ♪
♪ AND SIP THEIR LEMONADE ♪
♪ (WHEN THE SUN
SHINES DOWN) ♪
♪ WHEN THE SUN SHINES,
WHEN THE SUN SHINES ♪
♪ RAIN, I DON'T MIND ♪
♪ ♪
♪ SHINE, THE WEATHER'S FINE ♪
♪ I CAN SHOW YOU THAT
WHEN IT STARTS TO RAIN ♪
♪ (WHEN THE RAIN
COMES DOWN) ♪
♪ EVERYTHING'S THE SAME ♪
♪ (WHEN THE RAIN
COMES DOWN) ♪
♪ I CAN SHOW YOU,
I CAN SHOW YOU ♪
♪ RAIN, I DON'T MIND ♪
♪ ♪
♪ SHINE, THE WEATHER'S FINE ♪
♪ CAN YOU HEAR ME, THAT
WHEN IT RAINS AND SHINES ♪
♪ (WHEN IT RAINS
AND SHINES) ♪
♪ IT'S JUST A
STATE OF MIND? ♪
♪ (WHEN IT RAINS
AND SHINES) ♪
♪ CAN YOU HEAR ME,
CAN YOU HEAR ME? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ SDAEH RIEHT EDIH DNA NUR
YEHT SEMOC NIAR EHT FI ♪
♪ (RAIN) ♪
♪ NIAR (RAIN) ♪
♪ ♪